YOUNG JIN KIM

4C/ 196 Hobson St Auckland CBD Auckland 1010 Mobile: 021-039-3714

Email:YJKIM5426@gmail.com

Personal Statement

Experienced working with numerous programmers in IT areas for 2 and half years. Acquired project background knowledge and possessed super passion on programming, flexible, positive, good personality and good interpersonal skills. Learning and sharing knowledge on new technologies through Meetups.

Education

Work Talk class

Jan 2018 - Feb 2018

Graduate diploma on web development in Unitec

Mar 2016 - Nov 2017

- o Programming Fundamentals (Python)
- Introduction to Databases (MS-SQL)
- o Multimedia and Website Development (HTML, CSS)
- Data Warehousing (MS-SQL)
- o Programming Principles and Practice (JAVA)
- GUI Programming (C#)
- Information Systems and Analysis (SDLC)
- o Internet and Website Development (HTML, CSS, JS)
- Mobile Software Development (Android)
- Agile & Lean Software Delivery
- Advanced Program Development (C#)
- Web Application Development (ASP.NET CORE)
- Bachelor of information system in Kyungpook national university in Daegu Korea

Mar 2003 – Dec 2010

Compulsory military service

Aug 2004 - Aug 2006

Skills Summary

- Developed a shopping mall web site using ASP.NET CORE.
- Developed an individual blog using bootstrap.
- Developed a window application using Java.
- Developed a window application using C#.
- Experienced in Agile Environment (Scrum)
- Experienced in Continuous Integration Environment Git, Github
- Gained knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MS-SQL, Python

Professional experience

Accounting in Oriana in Auckland New Zealand

Apr 2015 - Feb 2016

- GST part
- SAP Financial consultant in LG in Seoul Korea
 - o Maintaining SAP system financial module

Jan 2011 - Apr 2013

Training Course

• Work Place class

Feb 2018 – Current